funtru.com 2017-12-21

# Privacy Policy - Funtru

This Privacy Policy controls the way we collect, use, maintain, and disclose information related to its users. This Privacy Policy applies to this website (www.funtru.com) and all the services provided by it.

### How do we gather users information?

We can collect information related to the personal identification of users in the following (but not limited to) ways: -

  * When the user comes to our website,
  * Fills a form on our website,
  * Subscribes to the newsletter,
  * Answers to a survey,
  * Contact us

Users can be asked for their name, e-mail address etc. as needed. We only collect the user's personal information when they voluntarily send us through any medium. Except for certain essential activities related to the website, they can use our website anonymously, without giving personal information.

When users use our website, we can also collect their non-personal information. Non-personal information includes the name of the browser, the technical information related to the user's computer, information related to the mobile (if the website is used on mobile phones), the name of the Internet service provider etc.

We adopt appropriate measures of security for collecting, maintaining and processing information related to the user, so that they remain unauthorized access, disclosure and change.

### Cookies

Our [website](http://www.funtru.com/ "funtru.com") can use cookies to improve user experience. The user's web browser saves the cookies in the memory of the device for the purpose of recording. The user can prohibit cookies from the settings of the web browser or can set a warning when cookies are sent. If they do this then the website may not work properly.

Our website can show ads directly to any advertiser or through its subsidiary. The advertiser or its assistant can use cookies to show their ads in a fair and profitable way. All cookies collect the user's non-personal information.

### How do we use the information gathered?

The website collects user information for the following purpose: -

  * For the user's service improvement,
  * To personalize user experience,
  * To improve our website,
  * To send e-mail regarding services or products.

### Sharing of personal information

We do not commercially use (selling or leasing) your personal information. We can share aggregated demographic information, which is not related to any personal information of the user, with our professional partners, trusted affiliates, and advertisers for the above use.

### Privacy Policy Change

Our [website](http://www.funtru.com/ "funtru.com") is free to make changes to your privacy policy at any time. If there is a change then we publish its notification on the main page of our website. We encourage our users to be conscious about our policy on the privacy of their personal information. Periodically reviewing this privacy policy and being aware of any changes is the ultimate responsibility of the user.

### Your acceptance on our terms

When using this website, you express support for our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this policy. If there is any change in our privacy policy while using you, it will also be considered your acceptance of the policy.

### Contact us

If you have any questions related to the privacy policy of our [website](http://www.funtru.com/ "funtru.com"), then you can contact us through the contact form given on our website.
